businesslistings.net.au 2019-03-31

# Privacy policy - BusinessListings.net.au - Add you business for free

BusinessListings.net.au collects client information to improve your advertising experience and to communicate with you about our products, services, and promotions. 

###  What informaion does BusinessListings.net.au collect

We collect information on our site visitors collectively including which sections of the site are most frequently visited, how often and for how long. This data is always used as aggregated, non-personal information. BusinessListings.net.au utilises this information to improve and enhance our services by monitoring the areas on the site which are most popular to you. This aggregated information may be shared with BusinessListings.net.au. 

For BusinessListings.net.au advertisers, we collect information, such as name, email address, phone and credit card numbers from you if you purchase advertising on our website. We maintain a record of your product interests and the purchases you make on line or by phone. If you just visit BusinessListings.net.au to search, we do not automatically collect any information. 

###  How does BusinessListings.net.au use my information? 

When you make a purchase from BusinessListings.net.au, we use your personal information to process your order, send you emails to confirm your order or to contact you via phone or email if we have other questions regarding your advertising purchase. 

When you place an advertisement or save your information on line, we will use your email address to send you information about your products, services, and promotions and to help us learn more about your advertising preferences. You always have the choice not to receive marketing information or calls. 

We may also contact you, subject to the choices you have made, via email, or telephone, to conduct market research and learn more about how we can improve our product offerings. 

###  How is my information stored? 

BusinessListings.net.au takes all reasonable steps to ensure the security of our system. BusinessListings.net.au allows you to access your information at any time, to keep it accurate and up to date. Any information which we hold for you is stored on secure services that are protected in controlled facilities. 

In addition, our employees and the contractors who provide services related to our information systems are obliged to respect the confidentiality of any personal information held by BusinessListings.net.au. However, BusinessListings.net.au will not be held responsible for events arising from unauthorised access of your personal information. 

You can also play an important role in keeping your personal information secure, by maintaining the confidentiality of any pass word and accounts used on the BusinessListings.net.au site for the purpose of advertising. Please notify us immediately at support@businessListings.net.au.com.au if there is any unauthorised use of your account by any other internet user or any other breach of security. 

###  Does BusinessListings.net.au share my information with third parties? 

We use a third party advertising company to serve ads when you visit our website. This company may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visit to this website in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third party advertiser may place or recognise a unique "cookie" on your browser. 

###  How do I change my or delete my listing?

You can review, change or delete certain personal information related to your use of our site (eg, name and contact information). For advertisers, simply click "member login" after logging into the advertiser directory and you will be able to edit your personal information. You can also ask us to update your personal information by emailing or calling our Customer Service centre. Please be sure to include your email address, full name and pass word. Please note that any requests to update your personal information may take up to two business days for your email request. 

###  What are cookies? How does BusinessListings.net.au use cookies?

A cookie is a small data file that websites often store on your computer's hard drive when you visit their sites. A cookie may contain information, such as a unique user ID that websites use to track the pages of the sites you have visited. We use cookies but do not store personally identifiable in your cookie. 

We use cookies in order to improve your search and advertising experience. Cookies enable us to keep track of your search preferences and advertising selections as you use our site. 

You can refuse cookies by turning them off your browser. If you turn off cookies, though, we will not be able to track your order to enable you to purchase advertising from our site. Nor will we be able to recognise you as a registered advertiser, which allows you to access your account information. 

###  Is my information secure?

Protecting your advertising order information is important to us. BusinessListings.net.au uses Secure Pay's Internet Payment Gateway to provide a secure environment for the authorisation of credit card transactions over the internet. Confidential information including client credit card details are encrypted the moment they are transmitted from the clients browser to the banking network using industry standard SSL (Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology) 128-bit RC4 encryption technology. 

A clients credit card details are not stored anywhere on the internet and the only company who has access to this data is the merchants bank. The bank also sends confirmation information via the same encryption technology back to the clients browser. These secure processes provide clients with peace of mind when purchasing on line. 

Some versions of browser and some firewalls do not permit communication through secure servers like the ones we use to process orders at BusinessListings.net.au. To check the security of your connection, look at the lower left hand corner of your browser window after accessing the server. If you see an unbroken key or a closed lock (depending on your browser), then SSL is active. You can also double check by looking at the URL line of your browser. When accessing a secure server, the first characters of the site address will change from "http" to "https". 

If your browser of firewall doesn't support SSL you will not be able to connect to the server, which means you wont be able to mistakenly place an order through an unsecured connection. If you cannot access the secure server for any reason, please contact us. 

###  What about links to other websites and services?

The BusinessListings.net.au website and its advertisements may contain links to other sites. BusinessListings.net.au does not control the privacy policies or practices of these websites. You should review those policies before providing any personal information. BusinessListings.net.au is not responsible for the content or practices of any linked websites, and we provide these links solely for the convenience and information of our visitors.
